hegre-art.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy - Hegre.com

Your privacy is important to us and a particularly high priority for the management of Hegre.com. We're committed to respecting your privacy and managing your personal information in a responsible manner.

Our privacy policy explains the personal information we collect and how we use this information. It also explains your rights to access, update or otherwise take control of the personal information we hold about you.

This policy was last updated on 25th May 2018 to reflect changes in European Union data protection laws. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Processing of personal data, including your name, address and email address will always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with other data protection regulations applicable to Hegre.com

## Hegre.com privacy principles:

Our Privacy Policy is fueled by our commitment to the following Privacy Principles:

1\. We’re deeply committed to creating a safe and secure online environment for you.  
2\. We do not sell or lease your personal information to third parties.  
3\. We strive to provide you with access to and control over the information you give us, and we take the protection of your information very seriously.  
4\. We do not display advertising for other services or goods than our own on Hegre.com.  

## Data security:

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. The personal information we hold is stored on secure servers in secure facilities within the European Union and the USA.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and unique. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out any information in public areas of the website. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the website.

## The information we collect:

We collect certain personal information in order to supply our services to you. On some pages, you can purchase a membership to Hegre.com, make requests or register to receive materials/online newsletters or be part of a promotion or contest etc. This kind of information is the first type of personal information collected and are typical name, age, email address, gender etc and are only information you choose to provide to us. We also record copies of your correspondence (including e-mail address), if you contact us. We use CCbill and Epoch's third-party credit card processing services, who also will obtain additional information typed by you in the case of you deciding to buy a membership subscription on our website.

The second type of personal information we collect is recorded automatically, through the use of cookies, pixel tags and other similar technologies. This information includes the link that directed you to our webpage, your IP address and geographical location, the types of device, operating system and web browser you are using and the date and time of your visit. The "Cookies" section of this policy explains more about how we use these technologies.

We do not collect personal information that is recognized as sensitive, such as information concerning health, ethnicity or political opinions and do not knowingly collect the personal information of any person under the age of 18. If we discover, or have reason to believe, we are holding sensitive personal information we will delete that information within a reasonable period.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the website or transmitted to other users of the website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although, we may limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed or used by unauthorized persons.

## Service providers:

We may share information with vendors providing contractual services to us, such as hosting vendors. We also may share your information, including your payment information, as appropriate to process your payments for the services or complete a transaction.

## Credit card info:

NOTE! The credit card info that you submit on the signup forms are submitted direct to the credit card companies and are not stored on our servers for security reasons. The signup pages are secure and encrypted.

## Site operations and analytics:

We use the following third-party partners to enable features that are necessary for providing you the services on our site and to allow us to understand how our services are being used, track site performance, and improve our services. To learn more about your rights with respect to these partners, including any opt-out rights, you can review their respective privacy policies.

Google Analytics <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>  
Amazon Web Services <https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/gdpr-center/>  
CCbill <https://www.ccbill.com/cs/policies/PP-consumer-english.html>  
Epoch <https://epoch.com/privacy.html>

## Affiliates:

We do not share your information with our affiliates.

## Cookies:

When you visit the Hegre.com website, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other browsing device. We use cookies to improve the quality of your experience, for storing your site preferences, improving search results and tracking user trends, such as how people surf the site. We also use cookies to determine if the user is logged in as a member or not. These cookies do not contain any private information and can not be traced back to you as a user in any way.

## Local storage & other tracking technologies:

We, along with third parties, may use other kinds of technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as “Flash cookies”) and HTML5 local storage, in connection with our Services. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your device and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these technologies may make use of different parts of your device from standard cookies, and so you might not be able to control them using standard browser tools and settings. For HTML5 local storage, the method for disabling HTML5 will vary depending on your browser. For Flash cookies, information about disabling or deleting information contained in Flash cookies can be found here: <https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html>

## The way we use information:

The information collected by Hegre.com is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your membership account or subscription to our mailinglists. WE DO NOT sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data or email address. The information collected by CCBill and Epoch are only used by us for the purpose of processing payment of your membership to Hegre.com and documentation for accounting and tax purposes.

We may also use your personal information to send you emails with selected offers, which we feel may be of interest to you. If you decide you no longer want to receive these emails, you can opt out at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link available in all these messages. Please note that it may take up to 48 hours for your opt-out to take effect and bear in mind that if you enquire about new products and services you may be opting back in to receive emails from us.

We'll also use your personal information to respond to any comments, requests or questions you may send us or to send you important messages we feel you should be made aware of, such as a significant change to this policy. We may also use your personal information to compile statistics of our marketing campaigns, in order to give us a better understanding of their performance and help us operate and improve our services. We may also share personal information with companies under the same ownership as us.

In general, we use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 

  * to present our Website and its contents to you;
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * to manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * to provide you with notices about your account or subscription, including expiration and renewal notices;
  * to notify you about changes to our website or any products or services we offer or provide through it;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features on our website;
  * to perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * to determine whether users of the website are unique, or whether the same user is using the Website on multiple occasions;
  * to track usage throughout various components of the website (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the website, etc.)
  * to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, demographic patterns, etc.
  * to communicate with you about products or services that may be of interest to you from us;
  * to develop and display our website content tailored to your interests;
  * to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * diagnose or fix technology problems;
  * to enforce our terms and conditions;
  * to manage our business;
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; 
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

## Transfers of personal information abroad

In order to deliver our services to you, we sometimes need to share your personal information with parties outside the European Economic Area (EEA). We'll always ensure that any transfers of this nature are fully compliant with European Union data protection laws governing transfers of personal information outside the EEA, so that your personal information is secure.

Some countries outside the EEA have been recognized by The European Union as having appropriate laws and safeguards protecting personal data, known as Adequate Jurisdictions, so that personal information may be freely transferred to them. The current list of these countries is Andorra, Argentina, Canada (commercial organisations), Faroe Islands, Guernsey, Israel, Isle of Man, Jersey, New Zealand, Switzerland, Uruguay and the USA (limited to the privacy shield framework). Personal information may also be transferred to countries not recognized as Adequate Jurisdictions, provided we inform you of the absence of appropriate safeguards to personal data in that country and you give your explicit consent to the proposed transfer. If we need to transfer your personal information to one of these countries, we will inform you in a clear, concise and transparent manner and will only make the transfer when you have given us explicit consent to do so.

## Other parties in connection with a corporate transaction:

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event that we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party, such as in the event of a merger, acquisition, or in connection with a bankruptcy reorganization.

## With your consent or at your direction:

In addition to the sharing described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties whenever you consent to or direct such sharing.

We also may share other information with third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users, including, for example, aggregated data about how users are using our Services.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We may modify or revise our privacy policy from time to time in our sole discretion and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this privacy policy, you are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version found at <http://www.hegre.com/privacy> so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.

If we change anything in our privacy policy, the date of change will be reflected in the “last updated date”. You agree that you will periodically review this privacy policy and refresh the page when doing so. You agree to note the date of the last revision to our privacy policy. If the “last updated” date is unchanged from the last time you reviewed our privacy policy, then it is unchanged. On the other hand, if the date has changed, then there have been changes, and you agree to re-review our privacy policy, and you agree to the new ones.

All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all access to and use of the website thereafter. The updated version of our privacy policy supersedes any prior versions immediately upon being posted, and the prior version(s) shall have no continuing legal effect. If you do not review new terms as posted, then you agree that you have waived your right to do so, and you are therefore bound by the updated conditions, even if you failed to review the new ones. You are on notice of changes, and your failure to review the amended terms is your own omission. By continuing to use the website subsequent to us making available an amended version of our privacy policy, you thereby acknowledge, agree to and consent to such amendment.

## How you can access or correct your information:

You can access and update all your personally identifiable information that hegre.com collects and maintains online by logging on to the "My Account" page on our site at: <http://www.hegre.com/profile>  
If you are unable to do so, you are most welcome to contact us via email on gdpr@hegre.com and we will help you.

If you are not a member but subscribe to our free online newsletters you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all newsletters we send out to manage your newsletter settings. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

If you would like to access/update your personal information stored by our third party credit card processors, you may contact them at any time on: [https://support.ccbill.com](https://support.ccbill.com/) or <https://epoch.com/find_purchase>

## How to contact us:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies or would like us to delete the information that Hegre.com store about you, please contact gdpr@hegre.com
